您真的不需要我们帮什么忙么  妈
Are you sure we can't help you with something, mom?
哦  不  你们两个小家伙就在这里给我好好坐着
Oh, no. You boys just sit here and do not lift a finger.
免得又磕了碰了  把什么东西打了
You might break one of them too.
我得去处理一下花园里面那堆事情
I am going to do some yard work.
遵命
You're the boss.
任务达成
Mission accomplished.
帕克的方法
The Parker way.
这机器真赞
It's beautiful.
您在干什么呢  鲁尼女士
Um, what are you doing, Mrs. Rooney?
哦  你懂的  把这些残枝断梗的
Oh, you know, just jamming these big branches
塞进这台一百马力的机器里面
into this hundred-horsepower monster
里面还有四十片不锈钢旋转刀片
with 40 razor-sharp stainless steel teeth.
哇
Whoa!
不会吧  我们能帮忙么
No way. Can we help?
呵呵  孩子  要是我不觉得你能把盘子放到水盆里面而不打掉
Oh, sweetie, if I can't trust you to carry your plate to the sink,
我怎么可能让你靠近这台机器呢
then I sure can't trust you around this bad boy.
此话当真
Seriously?
我没有比这更想做的事情了啊
But there is nothing I've ever wanted to do more.
话说  既然我这么想了  我要取消你的空手道课
You know, now that I think about it, I'm pulling you out of karate
我也要在你的自行车上重新装上从轮
and I'm putting the training wheels back on your bike.
好消息是  我帮你们买了蜡笔和安全剪刀
But the good news is... bought you some crayons and safety scissors.
就在里面  要我抱你进去么
They're inside. You want uppy?
做的不错啊  帕克
Nice work, Parker.
我们就连这个都做不成了
We got ourselves out of that one.
赞啊
Sweet!
这是那款 64 色的
It's the 64 pack.
盒子里面还有内建的卷笔刀呢
It has a sharpener built into the box.
哦  等等  你妈妈把那个也拿走了
Oh, wait. Your mom took that out.
耶  宝贝
Yeah, baby!
天  这听上去还真有趣
Man, that sounds like fun.
比这还有趣
More fun than all this?
这套里面有深棕黄色的蜡笔呢
Burnt sienna.
喔呼
Whoo-hoo!
我不敢相信她居然不让我们两个帮忙
I can't believe she's not letting us help.
正是
Exactly.
拜你所赐  她以后再也不会让我们做这种有趣的事情了
Thanks to you, she'll never let us do stuff like that again.
我们要不要击掌
Can a brother get a fist bump?
是不是说我如果什么都不做  就什么都做不成了
So if I don't ever do anything, I don't ever get to do anything?
这是我对帕克的方法的基本理解
It was my understanding that was the primary message of the Parker way.
看来帕克的方法存在指向错误
Well, perhaps the Parker way is misguided.
新鲜的玛芬蛋糕能不能然你觉得好过一点
Would fresh-baked muffins make this better?
当然
Certainly couldn't hurt.